Hey everybody, welcome back to Chance of Cenar.
I'm having a blast with this game so far.
I think we've been doing quite well in this area so far.
Let's keep it up.
I once again want to go back to the beginning here.
I just want to see if I got this one completely down.
So I come in here with boat, right?
I talk to these people, and I look like a weird, I don't know, person from a horror game.
Not a warrior though.
So he says greetings, or hello.
Question, are you a warrior, right?
That makes sense.
It's a question.
We know that it's confirmed, so he's asking are you a warrior?
Of course, the order here of the words makes it a little more difficult, right?
But he basically says, you are a warrior, I think, right?
As in question.
And then after that, she speaks and says, you are not warrior.
It could also mean him or her.
They are not warrior.
Because if she's answering a question, she would be speaking to this guy, right?
Maybe she wouldn't say you in that case.
I think I got the idea of this conversation down though, you know?
No, you're not a warrior.
Warriors love swords.
Although maybe in this case, Carrie would make more sense.
I don't know.
Warriors have swords, right?
Warriors are scary.
Yeah, is slash R.
I think I'm pretty on point with that one.
Okay.
I feel like I have maybe missed a conversation somewhere.
There's like a...
Also, what are these for?
These jelly beans.
These chili bananas.
I can't speak to her over there.
Let me see what you are saying again.
Also want to go back to the big area in the center.
Greetings.
I...
Hold on.
We are barts.
Right?
Because it's plural me.
We are barts.
And we...
Mirrors.
But wait, you're not carrying a mirror right now.
Okay.
You carry mirror?
Do you carry a mirror?
She's asking me.
Oh man.
Why would she talk about mirrors?
She's not holding a mirror.
She's painting.
Hmm.
I don't know.
Maybe it doesn't mean mirror.
What else could it mean though?
I don't know.
Let's head back to the big open area here in the center.
See if we missed something there.
Let's see these again.
What's up monkey?
What does this mean again?
Barts carry mirrors, right?
Warriors carry swords, yes.
And warriors are scary.
This is basically a repeat of the conversation that we had downstairs when we first arrived.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Yeah, okay.
Can I make you do it again?
Oh nice.
Barts love butterflies?
Warriors carry swords,
right?
But why is his hand going to the right?
And the sword is on the left?
That doesn't make any sense to me.
Wait a minute.
Barts carry...
But that's not a mirror.
That's a butterfly.
Yeah, he's scary.
Why are there stars up there?
Warriors are... confused maybe?
You know when you get bonked on the head in cartoons, they have stars circling over the head?
Maybe he's concussed?
I don't know.
Maybe they consider the warriors crazy or fanatics, you know?
Warriors are insane.
Ah...
I gotta say though...
Okay, so that was definitely a butterfly, wasn't it?
That didn't look like a mirror at all.
Hold on.
Where is it?
Mirror.
Oh, why is that page... Oh, here.
It could mean reflection.
Maybe they consider themselves...
butterflies?
I don't know.
I mean, this is definitely this, right?
We can agree on that.
Love.
It's gotta be love.
It's a freaking heart.
Love slash like.
Then again, you could argue that you could actually have love slash like...
in this one and it would make sense instead of carry.
You know, bards love mirrors.
Soldiers love swords.
What was the last one again?
Warriors are scary, right?
Yeah, warriors are scary.
Scary or crazy or, you know...
wild, I don't know.
And what else do we have?
Right, these three.
Oh, we actually only have these two pages here.
That's it.
What does this mean?
I'm hungry.
I'm rubbing my belly.
Hold on, what do we have here?
Is.
Our.
Me.
I think I tried that one, but didn't quite work.
Also, we have to consider the fact that a lot of these look like each other.
Oh, actually, that's not true what I'm saying because I was about to say...
if there's something like this, then the others over here need to be sort of similar.
Meaning, one of these lines needs to go through the horizontal line.
But that's not the case, actually.
So, never mind.
This could be anything.
This could be...
What would fit here?
Honestly, either...
me, like...
the concept of I...
or hungry.
I mean, we found bananas and stuff, right?
The monkeys are hungry?
The concept of hunger?
Let me go check the other... there's two other monkeys.
Let's check those out.
See if we can't figure that out.
Hey, monkey, I got a banana for you.
You want a tasty banana?
Look what I got.
Chili banana.
That's right, eat it.
What?
Me and Bart.
I am Bart.
Okay, that one makes sense.
Ah, but I could be wrong about me here, though.
Right?
I could be wrong about that.
Um...
Me... Have I seen that symbol before?
Looking like an E.
I mean, I have, of course.
It's here.
So this is a...
negative sentence.
So...
I...
Me not?
Wait, what?
What is that one?
Hold on.
That's a... magnifying glass.
You don't like it?
You like this?
You like flowers?
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I don't see anything about a mirror in this.
Maybe I got mirror wrong.
I wish these would stay.
Magnifying glass.
I cultivate flower?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Maybe they love symmetric things.
Butterflies are symmetric.
The flower looked pretty symmetric.
They like symmetry.
Symmetry.
Oh, wait a sec.
Let me actually keep mirror for now.
But...
Symmetry.
Or reflection.
But that's pretty much the same as mirror, I guess.
And this...
So what would that mean?
I...
Something symmetry.
But I could be wrong about me.
That's the problem here.
Shit.
We have another banana.
Let's go talk to the last monkey.
Perhaps that will give us the Rosetta Stone we're looking for.
Hey, yo, monkey.
I got banana for you.
Look at this.
Yeah, eat it.
Okay, that's Carrie.
Maybe I got him switched around.
What?
Bard's love music.
Yeah.
Or Carrie music.
You know what?
I probably got those switched around.
Because here the arms are clearly displayed.
This becomes love-like.
And then the other one that I had.
For Carrie.
Wait, where's that?
Carrie?
Wait, what?
Am I blind?
Oh, of course, that one.
Carrie.
So that's Carrie.
And this is wrong.
Here.
This one has to be... I think I'm right about me.
I'm not!
Okay.
Oh, man.
Let's see the others here.
Warriors carry swords.
What does that mean?
Fear carries... Hold on, would that make sense?
Let's see this again.
Warriors carry swords.
Yes.
That's being displayed, right?
Sauce?
Okay, I think I got fear slash scary wrong here.
Also, what is this last symbol?
Something scary carries something.
Well, that doesn't make sense.
Fear slash scary, I think I got that wrong for sure.
Let's put two stars on that just to signify that we're very unsure about that one.
And the last one, barts...
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Barts carry...
Maybe I got those mixed... Maybe music is instrument here.
Because you don't carry music, right?
God, I hope I didn't just fuck myself by switching carry and love.
Maybe I had it right.
So, what?
Who is this?
Who is that?
Okay, warrior...
Okay, warrior bard.
And who is this?
We need to figure out who this is.
I can't tell.
Let me get another look.
Who are you?
Is someone with a sad mask?
I don't know what that is.
Okay.
Oh!
It's her!
Also, wait a minute, we got some new ones here.
Wait a minute, look at her!
Servants!
Right?
Hold on.
Servants carry tools?
Fear scary.
Fear...
Servant?
Or, I don't want to say slave.
Maybe it's not that crazy here.
It's more like a servant, right?
Weapon?
Silly?
Clown?
Carry.
Boom,
that one is for sure.
Oh, I already have something for sword, but this is an axe.
But I guess this probably means weapon and not sword.
Now this...
Confused?
Acting...
Hey, look at this.
Entertainer?
What do I have?
Servant...
Demon?
Are you a demon?
Okay, that one I'm not sure about, but hold on a minute now.
I wish that when you moused over these, you could see what they were called.
Why is that not a thing?
Why do I have to find it over here?
Every time?
That seems like an oversight, doesn't it?
So, love slash like.
This one is symmetry, I think.
Mirror or reflection.
Then again, this could represent me, meaning myself.
I wonder if some of the sentences would make sense, that people are saying to me, if that's the case.
I feel like with the current me that I have, a lot of the sentences make sense.
But that could be a red herring.
So I gotta be on the lookout for that.
Okay, bards carry.
So I think music may be instrument instead.
But do I have another one for instrument?
Did I mark that somewhere?
I did, I did.
Hold on a minute.
Let me try and look at these glyphs in more detail.
The ones that I have confirmed.
Here.
Bard.
Oh, dude.
Look at this.
This is a person, right?
Because this line goes through the horizontal line.
But look at this top part here.
You see that with the line here and the two down?
They are kind of similar looking because they have similar sort of meanings.
You know, warriors and weapons are related.
Bards.
Instrument.
That makes so much sense.
Now I don't know if this is instrument or music though.
Okay, so this is demon I think.
I guess I put that in.
So me, let me look at these other glyphs now.
You.
Okay.
Servant.
Oh, that would actually make sense with the very first conversation we had.
They are asking, hey, is that a warrior?
Is that a servant?
You know?
I want to go back to the music people that I saw.
I want to revisit that conversation.
I think it was up here.
Yeah, here we go.
What are you guys saying?
Let me see.
He says, greetings.
Hello there.
With the current we have.
We love instruments.
Yeah, you wouldn't say that, would you?
And then she's asking, do you carry a... Okay, that doesn't make sense then.
But I guess it's like I could either have carry switched with love, or I could have music switched with instrument and both of these make sense.
But the current configuration that I have is wrong.
So I either have to switch music to instrument or carry to love for this to make sense.
Unless it's like a saying, hey, do you carry music?
You know, I don't think so.
So what do we switch here?
Let's see.
Let's try and switch music to instrument and vice versa.
This becomes music.
And the instrument becomes...
Oh, I can never find them.
My goodness.
Shit, I forgot which one I just switched.
Damn it!
Oh, it's this one.
Okay, so it's like that.
Instrument.
So let's see now.
We love music.
You carry an instrument?
Or maybe carry means...
Yeah, it has to mean carry.
I was about to say, maybe it means do you play an instrument?
But no, carry makes sense in all the other contexts, right?
So let's take a look at the book again.
Greetings.
This is carry.
Interestingly, looks like an inverted sword symbol.
A little bit.
What does this mean?
Someone who is confused.
Or is this person trying to be scary?
Huh.
I want to go back to the people that are like cosplaying as scary people.
That was that one guy going, rah!
Remember?
Let's see that one again.
Also, let me have another look up here.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You know what this also could mean?
Could mean beauty.
They appreciate beauty.
They are bards, right?
And symmetry is inherently something that we consider beautiful.
Oh my god.
It has to be that, or at least something like it.
Let's put beauty.
Uh, shit.
I don't think Mira is correct here.
Symmetry or beauty?
This has to mean music.
This...
Yeah, I don't know.
Emotion maybe.
Happy.
I like what I currently have.
Even though mask seems a little...
I don't know.
I mean, he's wearing a mask.
I'm a demon!
Oh!
Yeah!
I'm a demon!
I am!
So, is or am, I guess.
It's like, to be or not to be.
Music.
Um...
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Music?
Is shaped like that, almost like a wave.
Do we recognize that anywhere else?
Kind of?
Ah, not really, actually.
I have no idea what that is.
Or that.
I forgot where I found these.
Yeah, this is...
Like, I think I nailed this sentence here.
He's definitely saying, I'm a demon!
Right?
And they're like, whoa, that's so good.
So lifelike.
I was scared there for a moment.
Let's go back to the beginning and see if servant is correct.
Oh, let's talk to her again.
I know I'm going in circles here, but this is tough, guys.
Okay?
I'm having issues.
I am... or we are bards.
But then again, bards is not plural here.
It's the me that's plural.
So, does that make sense?
We are bards.
That doesn't make sense.
So that means I most likely got me wrong.
It just makes so much sense in every other sentence out there.
So I'm hesitant on removing it from my guess.
We love beauty.
You love beauty?
Yeah, beauty is music, art, you know, all the subjective stuff.
Yeah, I'm starting to get somewhere here.
Hmm.
I have a feeling there should be a plural in front of bard here.
Or remove the plural in the center.
And again, let's not start thinking the game is wrong.
How about we start thinking our guess is wrong?
First and foremost.
Let me see you.
Now that we know that is different.
I love beauty.
I'm beautiful.
Oh, that makes sense.
That makes so much sense now.
I think I got it.
So, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Love.
Beauty.
This could mean...
is RM.
Yes!
To be!
Exactly.
Oh my God, I fucking nailed that.
Dude.
Beauty?
Okay, I didn't write beat technically here, but it was close enough, right?
Frickin' yeah, dude.
And here...
This has to...
This has to refer to...
the guy going, I'm a demon, right?
He's like, with his hand, rar!
Acting crazy, even though this is more...
clowny than scary, in my opinion.
You know?
We can try, demon.
It's not right.
Okay.
I had a feeling.
Sometimes you gotta try it.
Okay, let's see here now.
You... be warrior?
Haha, right?
And then she says...
No, you be not warrior.
Haha, warriors carry swords!
You must be a servant!
No, no, wait, wait.
Warriors are servants.
No, that doesn't make sense, actually.
Hold on, I think I got servant wrong here.
I think I'm totally off base with servant.
Especially because servant would be a person.
Just like, uh, demons, humans, bards, and soldiers.
And this symbol right here does not go through the horizontal line.
Yeah, I'm totally off base here.
I'm gonna put, uh, scary back.
Even though I'm not quite sure it works.
It works in this context.
Right?
Warriors are scary.
What else could warriors be?
Other than scary.
Tall.
They could be intimidating, but that's the same thing.
Warriors are...
dressed differently.
Not beautiful?
Hahaha, they're ugly?
I don't know.
Maybe they consider the way of the warrior ugly, right?
Probably not.
Let me see, now that I have that confirmed, let me see your sentences here.
Yeah.
This, I think I'm on point with me there.
Now this, man, what could that mean?
Sword carry.
Oh, acting scary instead of...
I just don't want to try every combination here from the get-go, right?
But from everything else I've found, this makes sense to put in.
Fucking got it.
Idiot?
Who cares?
I was not expecting that.
Wow!
So they're just like, man, warriors are idiots.
Damn!
Okay.
That I did not expect.
I was going to say though, if it wasn't for this hand right here, I would have guessed clown.
Or like, yeah, idiot, someone who is, you know...
acting stupid.
But this claw right here made me think he's trying to cosplay as someone scary, you know?
But I guess not.
Okay, so far we fucking nailed it.
We got everything.
So now I want to go back out here and see these sentences again.
Even though I think I'm still missing one word from here or was it two?
Let's see.
Hello.
Yeah, okay.
Wait, what?
Oh, interesting.
What?
The translated versions are still in the wrong order.
But I guess maybe for them it's the right order?
This sounds like Yoda.
Idiots, warriors are.
Weapons, warriors have.
Warrior, you are not.
That's amazing.
What the actual fuck?
That is truly unexpected.
Especially the idiot part was so unexpected.
Okay, let me see the monkey again.
Things are clicking into place here.
Beauty, the bards love.
I'm not going to do the Yoda voice all the time.
Weapons, the warriors love.
Stupid, warriors are.
Okay, okay.
I would not have guessed stupid from this either, honestly.
Maybe from the head-tilding left and right, you know?
Silly.
So I guess idiot and stupid are interchangeable here.
Which I guess makes sense, based on context.
Now you.
Let's do that again.
I am not a scientist.
I take care of plants.
I am barred.
The lens.
I think that means scientist.
Oh, but then again, it doesn't go below the horizontal line.
Maybe science.
Yeah, we don't love science, we love art, right?
That makes so much sense to me.
Ah, wait, wait, we don't say I am not science.
That doesn't make sense either.
I am not scientific.
That could work in this context, you know?
Scientific?
I am not.
The other one here.
I need to see it again.
I disregard science.
Get it away from me.
I...
Something beauty.
Beauty, I...
Grow.
Appreciate.
What is he doing to the flower?
He is sustaining it.
Taking care of it.
You know what?
Let's just put that in.
Let's just say...
What's another word for taking care of something?
Taking care.
Cultivate.
Look after.
You know, something like that.
I don't like this right now.
Very much, but I am going to keep it.
I take care of beauty.
I grow beauty.
Because it is a plant.
Does that make sense?
Would anyone say that?
Beauty, I grow.
Beauty, I...
Oh, I don't know, man.
Yeah, this one is something... Grow.
Cultivate.
I don't know.
Grow, cultivate.
Let's just keep it at that.
It is probably wrong, but it is in the right ballpark, I think.
Of meaning here.
I cultivate beauty.
This is what we practice.
We practice beauty.
Maybe.
You know, like the scientists practice science, these guys practice beauty.
It is their craft.
Oh, wait, we create beauty?
We make beauty happen.
They planted a flower which became beautiful.
Make.
I would say grow is way too specific here.
We need to go more like vague.
Let's go make.
Create.
Especially because we have had that sort of word in the other languages before, right?
I think I am on point with demon here, by the way.
That one is so correct.
Science.
Where is beauty again?
I want to see beauty.
This one.
Beauty, okay.
Yeah.
This one doesn't quite make sense, though.
I am not inquisitive.
I am not empirical.
I am subjective based.
Science.
It could be scientific.
The meaning could be scientific.
A scientific I am not.
Right?
I can see that be a thing.
Context based.
Does it make sense in the sentence?
Now, the woman coming walking over there is intriguing me a little bit.
A weapon the warrior carries.
Ooh!
What does the idiot carry?
Or possess?
A saw?
A tool?
I don't know, a saw?
That's what it was, right?
Or a tool?
Hold on.
I wouldn't consider people who carry tools idiots, though.
Quite the opposite.
So, I am hesitant to put that down, but...
This one is for sure...
Right, I think.
Instrument.
Also, I feel like I am running out of places to go here.
Like, I feel kind of... Oh!
Never mind!
Holy shit, I missed this part!
Follow her!
Oh, shit!
I completely missed this part!
They are drinking the Golden Piss Vassa?
Wait, are there rivers literally flowing with wine?
That's crazy!
Okay, go this way first.
Oh!
Ooh!
It's a puzzle!
Oh, cool!
There?
Dude, I fucking nailed this puzzle!
Holy shit!
Wow, did I just get lucky or something?
Look at that, two hands.
I sawed you.
Oh, this is the language from...
From the Warriors.
You found me.
I sawed you.
Seek?
Search?
You make me?
Oh, you found me?
Wait.
Hold on a second.
This is supposed to be a direct translation, right?
I sawed you.
You found me.
Oh, find, of course!
Wait.
Am I wrong with make then?
I was like so sure about make.
Does that make sense with the flower we saw in the monkey business?
Beauty we find.
Actually, that could work!
Find?
You find me.
Yeah.
Uh, I seek you.
I sawed you.
So it's interesting that this up here is...
in the past tense.
But I guess maybe that doesn't matter.
Maybe this is like context based again.
Alright.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Yes!
Let's see here.
You?
Yes.
Seek?
Want?
Okay.
Me?
And find?
Fucking hell.
I'm so good at this game.
Nailed it.
Find, seek, want, you and me.
Beautiful.
Okay.
This thing though I have no idea what's going on with.
That is such a mystery.
Like obviously it's meant to fast travel but...
What's the TIE fighter about?
Connection is severed.
The warriors are trying to communicate with...
someone.
Oh, wait a minute.
Am I supposed to reestablish connections...
between all these cultures?
Bring them together?
Because these guys are definitely hating on the warriors.
I mean they're straight up calling them idiots.
Which is kind of funny because the warriors adore the bards.
They call them the chosen ones.
What an out of whack, out of balance relationship there.
Or dichotomy.
Right?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Music, instrument, demon.
Okay.
Let's go further down.
She's carrying bags.
Is this?
Oh, you're making tools.
Instruments.
Makes sense.
I think we got that one down.
Trumpets.
Flutes.
These are definitely servants.
Just the way they're walking as well is...
Okay, what do we have here?
Oh, that's easy.
Music.
Oh, happy sad.
Emotion.
Comedy.
Okay, that one I didn't expect.
But I guess it's closely related to emotion, right?
What did I guess before?
Mask?
Happy?
Music.
Instrument.
Beautiful.
Dude, I am rolling right now.
I only have two of them that I didn't confirm.
Not bad.
Can I somehow speak to you?
No, okay, instruments.
Um...
All right, let's go.
What if this piss-fosser is actually the...
the actual urine of the people that are presumably living above the bards?
It's flowing down and they're drinking it.
Oh, that's horrible.
Why am I saying this shit?
That's terrible.
Look, servant.
Right, servant.
Servant, for sure.
Wait, let me go up here.
That looks like a nice place.
I love the look of this whole area.
Oh, we got something new.
Okay, there's a dot beneath the horizontal line.
Do we have something like that anywhere else?
No, we don't.
That probably means something specific.
What's that?
Oh, it's the same one, okay.
It's just on both sides here.
Got it.
Okay.
What are you guys doing?
Oh, they're looking in the drain.
Did someone lose their keys?
Oh, you're sad.
I... I'm sad.
I'm repeating it twice.
Actually, repeating it once.
You want something?
Do you seek sadness?
Okay, that's probably not the actual thing they're saying here.
Um...
So they obviously dropped something down the drain.
Me...
Sad I am.
Huh.
Something you want?
That one is a little bit... of a mystery.
Maybe they're also searching for something that I also want?
What could he be saying?
There's only one word missing here.
I'm sad, I'm sad.
Do you seek sadness?
That doesn't make sense.
Why would he say that?
Like, hey, do you want to join us?
Be sad together?
A word that makes sense here but also makes sense there.
What could I possibly seek that he feels strongly about?
Me...
Uh...
Hmm...
Frustrated?
Do you seek frustration?
Why would he say that?
I'll be back.
Oh, wait, there's more!
Oh!
What?
Oh, that's the same one.
What am I looking at here?
The piss-vassa is flowing.
I'm like, I can't see it.
And then I take a look.
Wait, is something glowing there?
Oh, yeah!
Oh, what is that?
Ring!
Maybe he says, oh, my ring!
My ring!
He's exclaiming it, because he lost it, right?
And then he's saying, can you help me find it, or...
Maybe, can you see it?
He's like, my ring, my ring, can you see it?
Yeah.
Maybe me is also my, in this context.
Ring.
Or we can just call it jewelry.
Did I spell that right?
Jewelry?
Fuck, I don't know how to spell jewelry.
Ha ha!
I've never had to spell it in my life, I don't think.
Yeah, okay, that has to be that.
Or, you know, bracelet, whatever.
Something along those lines.
So the fact that the symbol down there looked like the symbol up here, could that mean sewer?
Why would they have a big sign saying sewer here, though?
This looks way too pretty to be...
a sewer.
At least this pavilion, or whatever.
You know?
Maybe it's the symbol for the wine they're drinking here, or the pizwasa.
Right?
Wine?
Water?
Very unsure.
Kind of disgusting, though, that they're drinking that straight from the source like that.
Where am I supposed to go?
Oh, there's a path over here.
Let's go for that one.
Go up there, sir.
Oh, someone's operating a boat?
And we have a sign.
Okay.
We don't know any of these.
One, two, three.
So these two are the same in front.
This could mean two.
You know, to the gate, or to the center.
And these other ones are the actual destination.
Two.
Very unsure.
I'm gonna say...
a place.
And this one is...
another place.
It's a place.
You just don't know what place it is.
What about you?
Hi, servant.
I do not have any...
something.
Tools?
No, wait, that will make you an idiot, right?
If you carry tools, apparently.
I don't have any...
So this is an object.
Some object.
Some item.
Oh, you're saying more.
You seek, want some item?
Could that also mean he's asking me to go grab that?
Like, can you go find it for me or something?
What are you missing?
I can try and look for whatever it is you want.
Oh, I can also click here.
Sir?
Do you mind stepping aside here?
I'm just gonna try and take off?
I think I need whatever item it is he's looking for to make this work.
Of course.
Maybe he's missing an engine.
He's missing...
I'm not sure what he's missing.
He's missing juice.
He needs some power.
That's a saw.
Huh.
I'm an idiot now.
Oh wait, no, sorry, sorry.
Servants carry tools.
I forgot what it actually said in the monkey display.
I got a saw now.
Oh, I got all kinds of saws.
I've got the saws, baby.
Got the marinara.
Alfredo.
A hammer.
Beautiful.
I'm just stealing all these tools.
Oh, what's that?
What's that?
There's more.
Oh, did I just replace it?
Oh!
He wants a specific tool, the guy out there, but...
What tool is it that he wants?
What's this?
He wants the hammer!
Smart.
And this is a...
a tweezer?
Whatever that's called.
I don't know what that's actually called.
I think it's a tweezer.
Tweezer.
Hammer.
And the tool... saw.
Nailed it!
What's it called?
Pliers!
Right, that's what I meant.
Saw.
Beautiful.
Simple tools.
Okay, you know what?
I take it back.
This area is actually kind of easy.
Compared to the others, I'm struggling way less.
Maybe it's because I'm just getting used to the game mechanics here.
That is a... drilling machine.
But I'm not wanting that right now.
This guy wants the hammer.
So let's grab the hammer.
Yeah.
Also, something else I noticed here.
Look at that.
There's a symbol up here that's sort of...
half gone.
But I guess it's for the saw that we already know about, so whatever.
Yeah, we're fine.
Okay.
I brought the hammer, bro.
A hammer, can you get?
A hammer I can deliver.
There you go.
Check this out.
Exactly what you asked for.
Nice.
Maybe they use greetings as thanks as well.
You are amazing.
Because I am amazing.
You'll be amazing.
Now he's going to ask for another tool.
You can go.
Okay.
Do I want to go?
Just yet?
Do I want to go just yet?
Sure, why not?
Okay, thanks.
And off we go.
Look at this weird contraption of a boat, huh?
They have such interesting...
mechanical inventions here.
Very over-engineered, it feels like.
Right?
Which is kind of funny for a...
a sect of bards.
Man, can I go slurp that wine right there?
No?
I want it bad.
Okay, let's head in here.
Oh, we got more stuff.
Guys, this area is freaking amazing.
I'm having a blast with this game.
I'm going to take a quick break and I'll be back in a sec.
Thanks for watching.
Bye-bye.